

Clément Boschet
FullStack Developer

Contact Me

🤳 +352 621 454 874

🖊 Ottange, France

clem.boschet@gmail.com

Follow Me







Languages

Native Speaker

₹ Good Working Level

Conversational Level

Interests





Sports

Books





Music

Travel

Profile

Developer in professional retraining. Throughout the first years of my professional path I worked as a consultant and growth manager in a franchise network. my thoroughness and my adaptability allowed me to lead missions in several areas. I have been passionated by computer science, since always, and I started to teach myself to programming one year ago. I have learned the basics of several languages (JavaScript, Java) and used different tools (VS Code, Eclipse, Git) in this journey.



Experience

Junior Consultant Franchise -Consulting Axe Réseaux

Franchise Manager TWC Développement Sept 2016 - Today

Sept 2015 - Sept 2016



Education

Master Marketing Franchise Management IGR-IAE Rennes Sept 2015 - Sept 2016



